<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Enactivity</title>
    <link>https://jamestingedwards.github.io/legis-hack/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Enactivity</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 13:45:04 +1200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jamestingedwards.github.io/legis-hack/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Law to XML</title>
      <link>https://jamestingedwards.github.io/legis-hack/projects/law-to-xml/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 13:45:04 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jamestingedwards.github.io/legis-hack/projects/law-to-xml/</guid>
      <description>The current flow and format The Parliamentary Counsel&amp;rsquo;s Office writes New Zealand enactments, using software tools which generate XML files. Those files are packed with detailed metadata to help with print layouts. But that extra data can get in the way of open-source, automated, and collaborative approaches to working with legislation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>XML to open law on GitHub</title>
      <link>https://jamestingedwards.github.io/legis-hack/projects/xml-to-github/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 13:44:39 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jamestingedwards.github.io/legis-hack/projects/xml-to-github/</guid>
      <description>Tracking changes online GitHub is a tool for sharing text. Most of that text is code, but it can also work for sharing legislation. It is a familiar tool for programmers, making it easy to track changes to code over time, and to talk about what changes make sense. Those are natural advantages for legislation as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://jamestingedwards.github.io/legis-hack/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 18:43:07 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jamestingedwards.github.io/legis-hack/contact/</guid>
      <description>The Code Our code is in a GitHub repository here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://jamestingedwards.github.io/legis-hack/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 18:42:58 +1300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jamestingedwards.github.io/legis-hack/about/</guid>
      <description>Law as Code As part of the Better Rules Hackathon, we wanted to help make legislation easier to use, track, and improve.
The Goal We wanted to build a proof-of-concept, to show that it is both feasible and beneficial to make legislation easier to work with.
The Approach We wanted to use simple, familiar tools, to make the most of our limited time over the weekend. We chose to push our output to GitHub, a popular platform for sharing and working with code, to avoid any need to manage our own web hosting.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>